master.ca 2017-04-10

# Privacy Policy | The Master Group

**PRIVACY**

At The Master Group (“Master”), your privacy is important to us. This statement sets out our privacy practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information on this site. Personal information is information that is personally identifiable to you. Personal information may include your name, e-mail address and mailing address, as the case may be. Visitors to this Web site are not requested to reveal any personal information. However, on a voluntary basis, you may provide and disclose personal information to us in using certain features of our site, such as the Careers section of this site. Master will never disclose, sell or lease to any third party, any personal information that you provide on this site without your permission, unless we are required to do so by law.

**Access**

If you have already requested to be part of a mailing list, you may cancel your profile by going back to the section where you created that request or by contacting us using the information provided at the end of this privacy statement. If you have previously provided us with personal information and wish to verify it or have the information removed from our records or corrected, please contact us using the information provided at the end of this privacy statement.

**Security**

Your personal information is treated as private, confidential information by Master and we strive to ensure that your personal information is protected at all times. To maintain the confidentiality of your personal information, this information is kept in a secure environment by Master. However, even though Master has implemented methods designed to ensure the protection of your personal information that are considered to be effective, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be lost, used unlawfully or modified in a fraudulent manner since no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely confidential. Consequently, we bear no liability for the use that may be made of the information by you or any third party.

**E-mail**

If you submit an e-mail inquiry to this site, any personal information you might submit at the same time will only be used by Master employees who need to have access to it in order to respond to your inquiry.

**Changes**

Master reserves the right to change this privacy statement as it sees fit and without prior notice. However, we will ensure that any change to this statement is in compliance with privacy laws in effect in Canada and is posted on this page.

**Data collection**

Master occasionally uses the Google, Facebook, AdRoll or other display advertising networks to collect visitor data on our site and then serve targeted display ads to you on other sites. Our partners use technology such as cookies and web beacons to collect this data. For more information or to opt-out of this type of advertising, please visit AdRoll’s privacy policy.

**External Links**

This site may contain links that take you to other Web sites. This privacy statement does not extend to the data collection practices of third parties and Master does not assume any responsibility for the privacy practices, policies or actions of third parties.

**Comments ans suggestions**

If you have any comments, questions or complaints regarding Master’s privacy statement or practices, please contact us at : webmaster
